People do not live
for the sake of clothing!
（皐月(さつき)）人は服のために
生きるのではない！
I, Kiryuuin Satsuki, am rising up
to overthrow Life Fibers!
この鬼龍院(きりゅういん)皐月 生命戦維(せんい)
打倒のために立ち上がる
本能字(ほんのうじ)学園は貴様を倒すために
つくった私の城だ
Honnouji Academy is the fortress
I created in order to defeat you!
覚えておけ 鬼龍院羅暁(らぎょう)
Remember that, Kiryuuin Ragyou!
I pretended to obey you
as I waited for this day to come.
貴様に従うふりをして
この日を待っていた
Fear is freedom!
恐怖こそ自由 君臨こそ解放
Control is liberty!
Contradiction is truth!
矛盾こそ真理
それがこの世界の真実だ
That is the reality of this world!
Listen well, you pig that serves clothing,
服に へつらう豚よ
その真実に屈服せよ
and bow before that fact!
You fool.
（鳳凰丸(ほうおうまる)）愚かな 身の程を知れ！
Know your place!
Not on my watch!
（蟇郡(がまごおり)）させん
Shackle Regalia Mk 2!
（蟇郡）縛(しばり)の装 改(あらため)！
SHACKLE
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
（鳳凰丸）うぐっ
Inumuta.
犬牟田(いぬむた) 全員を解放しろ
Release the audience.
（犬牟田）了解
Yes, ma'am.
Huh?
（薔薇蔵(ばらぞう)）おお？
（好代(すくよ)）一体 何だったの？
What was that all about?
（ガッツ）ガッツ？
Thank goodness!
（又郎(またろう)）よかった
父ちゃん 母ちゃん ガッツ
Dad, Mom, Guts!
What is this?
（鳳凰丸）これは…
（犬牟田）生命戦維の活動を
抑止するジャミング弾だ
Jammers that keep
Life Fibers in check.
I based them off
Nudist Beach's weapons.
ヌーディスト･ビーチの
武器を改良した
Impertinent high schoolers!
（羅暁）高校生風情が…
You'd best not look down on us.
（皐月）甘く見ないほうがいい
Every student here is a soldier that has been
trained to fight you—no, to fight Life Fibers!
ここにいる生徒は全て貴様と—
いや 生命戦維と戦うための
戦士として鍛えられている
Behold the might of Honnouji Academy!
本能字学園の力 見るがいい
Uh huh.
（縫(ぬい)）な〜るほど
こういうことだったのね
Now it all makes sense.
（縫）皐月ちゃん やるやる
Way to go, Satsuki!
...Your opponent here...
（猿投山(さなげやま)）貴様の相手は—
俺だ！
is me!
Blade Regalia Mk 3!
（猿投山）剣(つるぎ)の装 更改(さらにあらため)
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
BLADE
REGALIA MK 3
And who might you be?
どちら様？
One of Honnouji Academy's Four Devas:
（猿投山）本能字学園
四天王のうち 猿投山渦(うず)
Sanageyama Uzu!
I'm going to pay you back
for what you did to me last time!
この間の借りは—
返させてもらうぜ
EPISODE 18
INTO THE NIGHT
Satsuki's going to
take down her own mother?
（流子(りゅうこ)）皐月が母親を倒す？
That means we share a common goal.
（鮮血(せんけつ)）
我々と目的は同じということか
（黄長瀬(きながせ)）どうなってる これは
What the hell's going on?
Don't ask me.
（美木杉(みきすぎ)）いや 僕にも想定外だ
This is beyond my wildest predictions.
Matoi.
（モニター:蟇郡）
纏(まとい) 皐月様は—
Lady Satsuki planned to fight the
Life Fibers from the very beginning.
最初から生命戦維と
戦うつもりだった
But in order to trick Director Ragyou,
だが羅暁理事長を
たばかるためには—
she couldn't let even a shred
of her true intentions show.
髪の毛ほども本心を
見せるわけにはいかなかったのだ
Then why the heck did she
fight Nudist Beach and me?
（流子）じゃあ あたしや—
ヌーディスト･ビーチとの戦いは
何だったんだよ
（モニター:皐月）
なまはんかな味方なら必要ない
I have no need for half-baked allies.
If you can't beat my army,
我が軍に負けるようでは—
then you don't stand a snowball's
chance in Hell against the Life Fibers.
到底 生命戦維との戦いに
勝てるわけはないからな
（流子）何！
Say what?
If you don't like my methods, then I'll
gladly take you on after I'm done here.
（皐月）
私のやり方が気に食わないなら
あとで相手をする
However, if you have the resolve
to protect the freedom of man,
だが貴様に人間の自由を守るという
志があるなら—
then fight with everything
you've got for now.
今は全力で戦え！
（羅暁）フッ 大した志だな
I applaud your resolve.
Are you saying you don't mind stabbing
your own mother in the back to see it through?
母親を背中からだまし討ちしても
かまわぬというのか
That goes without saying!
（皐月）当然だ
I'll do whatever it takes
to defeat a monster like you.
貴様のような怪物を倒すためなら
どんな手でも使う
Call me a coward or a crook
all you want. I'd love that.
ひきょう奸物(かんぶつ)と罵られようと
望むところだ
Did you just call your
own mother a monster?
（羅暁）
実の母親を怪物呼ばわりか
I don't think someone who can shrug off a
stab through the heart has any right to disagree.
（皐月）
心臓を一突きにされても—
平然としている貴様が
言えたセリフではない
You became a monster the moment you threw away
your humanity and fused yourself with Life Fibers.
生命戦維と一体化し
人間であることを捨てた怪物が
I am no monster, young lady.
怪物ではない
より真理に近づいた—
I am a life-form that is
one step away from divinity.
生命だよ
What the heck?
（薔薇蔵）何だ ありゃ
（好代）ものすごく丈夫な人ですね
What a resilient lady.
（又郎）いやいや化け物(もん)でしょ
I think you mean "freak".
This is the truth behind Life Fibers.
（モニター:皐月）
これが生命戦維の正体だ
If this battle caught your eye, burn any
REVOCS-made clothing in your possession!
この戦いを見た者は
ＲＥＶＯＣＳ(リボックス)社の服を焼き払え
With your help, we can liberate mankind!
それが人間の自由のためだ
Pay me back? I don't remember
lending you anything.
（縫）
借りって何か貸してたっけ？
（猿投山）壊惨総戦挙(かいさんそうせんきょ)での
不意打ち 忘れたか
Did you already forget the sneak attack
you pulled on me during the Naturals Election?
（縫）ん… ごめんね
女は下着を替えると—
Sorry about that.
When a lady changes her underwear,
she leaves the past behind her!
過去も忘れるから
Do you really think you can beat me
just by getting a little facelift?
多少 衣がえしたところで
僕に勝てると思って…
Yes, I do!
（猿投山）ああ 思うね！
Hm?
See that?
（猿投山）見たか！
My eyes may have lost their light,
光を失った分
俺の剣は光を超えたのだ
but my sword's surpassed
the speed of light!
There you go,
running your big mouth again.
（犬牟田）またまた盛って話す
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
PROBE
REGALIA MK 2
It's impossible for humans
to move faster than light.
人間が光より速く移動するのは
不可能でしょう
However, it is possible to make
someone believe that you are.
ただし そう思わせることはできる
By leaving behind a clear afterimage while hiding
the actual body behind optical camouflage, that is.
残像を固定化し
光学迷彩で実体を消せばね
Optical camouflage is so computer geek.
（縫）自分は姿を見せないとか
パソコンオタクっぽいね
（犬牟田）うっ
（縫）気持ち悪いよ
It's totally creepy, I hope you know.
Let's have you stay put, shall we?
（蟇郡）ちょこまか
動かないでもらおうか
Oh? So it's three-on-one?
（縫）ふーん
３人掛かりってわけ
Nah.
（蛇崩(じゃくずれ)）いいえ ４人いるから
四天王って言ってんでしょう
Like I said before, we're called the Four Devas
because there are four of us!
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
That's the first time I've heard you say it!
初耳なんだけど
Oh, right. My bad.
あら失礼
（蟇郡）言っておくが
俺たちは しぶといぞ
I'll have you know
that we're a tough lot.
We could never be defeated
by the likes of you!
貴様ごときに ひざまずきはしない
How annoying.
うっとうしい 何かそういうの
...That tough-guy act...
really gets on my nerves.
ムカつく
Dad, Mom!
（マコ）父ちゃん 母ちゃん
I'm home!
（マコ）ただいま〜
Oh, Mako.
あら マコ おかえり
Welcome back.
（薔薇蔵）
生きてたか マイドーター
So you were alive, my daughter?
Yep!
I can't rest easy until I finish handing out
all these souvenirs from Osaka.
大阪土産 配るまでは
死んでも死にきれないよ
（又郎）さすが姉ちゃん
心得てるね〜
That's my sis.
You know where it's at.
（ガッツ）ガッツー
Time to dig in!
（満鑑飾(まんかんしょく)一家）いただきます
（蟇郡）フッ
またお前か 満鑑飾
What's the matter with you,
Mankanshoku?
What do you mean, "matter"?
（マコ）“また”って何が？
（又郎）又郎なら俺だい
If you mean "the Matarou
with you", I'm over here!
（蟇郡）
そんなことはどうでもいい
I couldn't care less!
Mankanshoku,
help the audience escape!
（蟇郡）満鑑飾
観客席のみんなを逃がせ
What?
ええー！ 私が？
Me?
（蟇郡）ここにいると危険だ
This place isn't safe right now.
We don't want to cause
any unnecessary casualties.
不要な犠牲者は
我々の本意ではない やれ！
Now get to work!
（マコ）はい
Right away, sir!
Ladies and gentlemen!
（拡声器:マコ）
皆さん 逃げてくださーい
Run away!
Back-Alley Doctor
Mankanshoku
All You Can Eat
Kansai Specialties
Check it out! We have
octopus dumplings from Kansai!
関西土産のたこ焼きだよ
串カツだよ 食べ放題だよ
And pork kebabs, too!
It's all-you-can-eat!
寄っといでー
Come one, come all!
When did you change your mind?
（羅暁）貴様…
いつ心変わりをした
（皐月）
心変わりなどしていない
I did nothing of the sort.
Ever since I grew old enough to make my own
decisions, I've lived in anticipation of this day.
物心付いたときから 今日の
この日のために生きてきたのだ
（羅暁）何だと
What did you say?
（皐月）
真実を知ったのは５つのとき
父は全てを話してくれた
I was five when I learned the truth.
Father told me everything.
About Life Fibers, COVERS,
and you: Kiryuuin Ragyou!
生命戦維 カバーズ
そして鬼龍院羅暁
He told me about your wicked goals.
貴様の忌まわしい所業の目的
全てをな
Everything.
He said to me,
（皐月）父は言った
This will be your wedding dress.
“皐月 これがお前の花嫁衣装だ”
"Satsuki, this will be your wedding dress."
"But the moment you put it on,
“だが これを着たとき—”
you will be enslaved by clothing."
“お前は服の奴隷になる”
FATHER
KIRYUUIN
SOUICHIROU
父は優秀な科学者だった
He was an ingenious scientist.
その能力を見込まれて
鬼龍院の家に婿に入った
His talents recognized,
he married into the Kiryuuin family.
And then he fathered a child: me.
そして私という子供をつくった
But I was only brought into this world to
be a test subject in Life Fiber experiments.
だがそれは生命戦維の
実験体にするためだったのだ
This isn't working.
（羅暁）ダメね １歳児では
遅すぎたわ やはりこの子に…
We shouldn't have left it
until she was a year old.
I suppose it will have to be this one.
The next year,
（皐月）翌年 生まれたばかりの
次の子供に—
they tried fusing their newborn
second child with Life Fibers.
生命戦維と融合させる実験を行った
Not even a body which carries my genes
can overcome its resistance to Life Fibers, huh?
（羅暁）
私の遺伝子を
持つ個体でも—
生命戦維への
拒否反応は否めないか
Oh well.
しかたない
That's when my father
...made up his mind...
（皐月）
そのとき父は決意したのだ
to rebel against the
Life Fibers and Kiryuuin Ragyou.
生命戦維と
鬼龍院羅暁に対する反逆を
At the end of the day,
he was just a plebeian.
（羅暁）所詮は凡人 装一郎(そういちろう)などに
宇宙の真理は理解できない
The likes of Souichirou could never
comprehend the truth of the universe!
My father was well aware
that you'd go after him.
（皐月）
貴様が手を打ってくるのは
父にもわかっていた
だから私に全てを託したのだ
That is why he left everything to me.
I can't believe he left a
five-year-old girl to do his dirty work.
（羅暁）
まさか５歳の娘を頼るとはね
（皐月）ただの５歳児ではない
It was no ordinary five-year-old.
Don't you dare forget that
it was me, Kiryuuin Satsuki!
この鬼龍院皐月である
ことを忘れたか
KIRYUUIN SATSUKI
I'll admit, you sure know how to talk big.
口だけは一人前だな
だが私を倒そうと
生命戦維は滅びんぞ
However, killing me
won't destroy the Life Fibers.
Are you talking about
the original Life Fiber?
原初(げんしょ)生命戦維のことか
If so, then I've already made my move.
ならば手は打ってある
You are members of
Honnouji Academy's Sewing Club, yes?
（揃(そろい)）本能字学園
裁縫部の皆さんですね
お待ちしておりました
I've been expecting you.
（伊織(いおり)）あれがカバーズか
Those are the COVERS, huh?
総員 瞬間凍結剤 噴射！
All hands, fire the
instantaneous coagulants!
I've put a stop to the
original Life Fiber's activities.
（モニター:伊織）
原初生命戦維の活動を
停止させました
How did insects like them
make it all the way underground?
あんなヤツらが地下まで
やすやすと
I took out Kuroido and
everyone else who served you.
（皐月）黒井戸(くろいど)たち 貴様の
手の者は全て私が倒しておいた
泊まった あの夜のうちにな
It was when I stayed the night there.
Ragyou!
羅暁 人類の解放のため
貴様の命はここでもらう
In order to free humanity
from its shackles,
I will take your life
right here and now!
Lady Ragyou!
（鳳凰丸）羅暁様 うっ
Out of my way!
邪魔だ！
（羅暁）皐月 貴様の兵たち—
...Satsuki. All of your soldiers...
belong to me now.
私が頂く
（生徒たち）わあ
That bitch!
（流子）あいつ…
生徒を操り人形にしやがった
She turned the students
into her puppets!
They've been mentally refitted.
（羅暁）精神仮縫いだ
MENTAL REFITTING
I sewed my Marionette Thread
throughout their brains.
彼らの脳を私の
しつけ糸で縫い付けた
Go forth, men.
やれ！ お前たち
Lady Satsuki!
（蟇郡）皐月様！
It matters not!
（皐月）かまわん！
襲ってくるものは全て敵と思え
Consider anyone that comes
after us to be an enemy!
Until we defeat Ragyou,
we must have minds of steel!
羅暁を倒すまでは
その心は鋼と化せ
人衣(じんい)圧倒 神衣(かむい)純潔
Life Fiber Override:
Godrobe Junketsu!
GODROBE
JUNKETSU
（皐月）ハァー！
...Wha—
ちょっ… 待ちやがれ鬼龍院
うわっ
Hold it, Kiryuuin!
Ryuuko.
流子君 ここは僕たちに任せて
羅暁を
Leave this to us
and go after Ragyou!
Uh, okay.
（流子）あ… わかった
Who would've thought Kiryuuin Satsuki
was planning a rebellion?!
（黄長瀬）まさか鬼龍院皐月が
反逆を企てていたとはな
But if that's the case,
（美木杉）だがこうなったら
羅暁を倒してくれれば誰でもいい
I don't care who takes Ragyou out!
Sheesh.
（黄長瀬）
まったく 何しに来たんだか
What did we even come here for?
（皐月）タァー
Kiryuuin Ragyou!
（皐月）
鬼龍院羅暁 逃がしはせん
There's no escape for you!
Very impressive, my girl.
Even if I do say so myself.
我が娘ながら大したものだ
But you've made some huge mistakes.
だが お前は大きな過ちを
犯している
Matoi!
（皐月）纏！
（鮮血）流子 糸がほどけない
Ryuuko, I can't unravel this thread!
（流子）この…
Your first one was
bringing this Matoi girl here.
（羅暁）例えば この纏の娘を
呼び寄せたことだ
（羅暁）戦力のつもりだった
かもしれないが—
Maybe you thought
she'd be of use to you,
but she's my pawn now.
こうすれば私の駒になる
Too bad for you.
残念だったね
She's this powerful without
activating Life Fiber Synchronize mode?
人衣一体せずに このパワーか
すばらしい
Marvelous.
Looks like this is what
she's truly capable of.
どうやらこれが
その子の潜在能力らしいね
ううっ この愚か者が
You damn fool!
（猿投山）もらった
Got you!
Mind's Eye: Critical Thrust!
心眼天穿(しんがんてんせん)突き
What?!
何？
Mon Mignon Prêt-à-Porter!
（縫）
モン ミニョン プレタポルテ
君たち真面目すぎるから
つまんない
You guys are too serious. Such a bore!
My adorable clones will play with you,
僕のかわいい分身たちが
相手してあげるから—
もう少し遊び心を覚えるんだね
so take this opportunity to learn
how to have a little fun, 'kay?
（流子）だあー
Get a hold of yourself, Matoi!
纏 しっかりしろ！
その子の脳神経は
特にキツく縛り上げている
I took great care to bind
her cranial nerves extra tight.
She cannot escape my control.
もう私の支配から
逃れることはできない
Matoi Ryuuko!
纏流子！
...Don't...
（流子）ナメるな〜！
...look down...
on us!
What?
何？
Quit making light of us!
（流子）甘く見るんじゃねえ
私と鮮血はこんな糸じゃ
縛りきれねえんだよ
This puny thread isn't anywhere
near enough to shackle Senketsu and me!
I don't believe it.
まさか 羅暁様の
精神仮縫いを破るとは…
How could she break free
of your mental refitting?
今の感触は…
...That sensation I felt just now...
（皐月）フッ さずがに私を
手こずらせるだけのことはある
No wonder you give me
such a hard time.
Talk about condescending.
どれだけ上から目線なんだよ
I've got a graveyard full of bones
to pick with you, woman!
いろいろ てめえには
文句はあるが…
But for now, I'm gonna kick her ass!
今はあいつをぶっ倒す
La vie est juste drôle.
ラ ヴィエ ジュストウ ドロール
Let's go, Senketsu!
（流子）いくぞ 鮮血
（鮮血）おう
...Life is truly...
（羅暁）まさしく人生は
droll!
面白い
Long time no see, Ryuuko!
（縫）久しぶり 流子ちゃん
...You bitch...
てめえ…
Harime Nui!
（流子）針目(はりめ)縫！
Satsuki said she was the one
responsible for killing your dad,
（モニター･･縫）
君のお父様殺したの
皐月ちゃんは—
自分のせいだって
言ってたけど—
but that was a great big fib!
全部 僕と羅暁様で
やったことだよ
It was all my and Lady Ragyou's doing.
I know you want this
Sword Scissor returned to you,
（縫）この片太刀バサミ
返してほしいんでしょ？
so why don't you avenge
your father right here and now?
お父様の敵(かたき)
ここで取っちゃおうよ
That said, don't get mad
when I turn the tables on you.
もっとも返り討ちに
遭っちゃっても怒らないでね
Kiryuuin.
（流子）鬼龍院 羅暁は任せた
I leave Ragyou to you.
I don't see why you get
to leave anything to me.
貴様に任される筋合いはない
Killing my mother has
always been my goal.
母を倒すのは私の大望だ
Life Fiber Synchronize:
（流子）人衣一体 神衣鮮血
Godrobe Senketsu!
GODROBE
SENKETSU
Have you always been this slow?
（流子）お前の動きは
そんなに遅かったっけ？
（縫）
モン ミニョン プレタポルテ
Mon Mignon Prêt-à-Porter!
Mere cloth is no match for me!
How could this be?
（縫）そんな…
What's the matter?
（流子）どうした どうした？
I've never seen you put on
such a serious face before.
てめえがそんなマジ顔するのは
初めて見るぜ
Ryuuko.
（鮮血）流子
（流子）どうした
What's up?
また調子に乗るなっつうのか？
Are you gonna tell me
not to get full of myself again?
No. It's the total opposite.
（鮮血）いや 逆だ
（流子）ん？
We've never been in such good shape.
（鮮血）こんなに
調子がいいのは初めてだ
You and I have become completely one!
私とお前は今
完全に１つになっている
This is truly life and fiber synchronized!
これこそ まさに人衣一体
LIFE
&
FIBER
SYNCHRONIZED
You can say that again.
This feeling is out of this world!
ああ 最高に気持ちいいな
LIFE
&
FIBER
SYNCHRONIZED
こんな力 なぜ普通の人間が…
How can a normal human be so powerful?
Out of my way!
（皐月）どけえ！
Kiryuuin Ragyou,
（皐月）鬼龍院羅暁 父 装一郎と
名も付けられなかった幼い妹
you killed my father, Souichirou,
and my little sister who you didn't even name.
You shall atone for that sin!
２つの命の償いしてもらう
So in the end, this is all a
mold-ridden plot for revenge?
結局 古色蒼然(こしょくそうぜん)のあだ討ちか
若いのにつまらないね
Such a boring aim
for someone so young.
Great causes are always
fuelled by personal desire!
（皐月）私情あってこその大義
With your heart bound by Life Fibers,
you couldn't possibly comprehend that!
生命戦維に心を縛られた
貴様には わかりはしない
Can you kill me?
私が倒せるか？
I don't care who or what you are!
...If I slice through your neck...
（皐月）いくら貴様でも
その首 落とせば生きてはいまい
you can't possibly survive!
Give me your head!
御首 頂戴
ハァー
Lady Ragyou!
（鳳凰丸）羅暁様
It's finished.
終わった…
これは…
What's happening?
Shirou!
（伊織）本能字学園 応答せよ
Honnouji Academy, do you copy?
Honnouji Academy!
（伊織）本能字学園…
Is it just my imagination?
（皐月）気のせいか…
You're the one who's finished,
（羅暁）終わったのは お前だよ
Satsuki.
皐月
（羅暁）首の皮一枚 いや
首の糸一本つながっていれば—
So long as a shred
...of the skin on my neck—
no, so long as a single thread
of my neck stays connected,
my body can regenerate.
私の肉体は再生できる
Not even your Bakuzan
could cut it off entirely, eh?
お前の縛斬(ばくざん)も完全に
斬ることはできなかったようだね
（皐月）そんな…
...How...
Lady Satsuki!
（四天王）皐月様
You shall not interrupt.
（鳳凰丸）邪魔はさせません
Satsuki, you seem to be
under a grave misunderstanding.
（皐月）ぬわっ
（羅暁）皐月…
お前は大きな勘違いをしている
その純潔 お前が
着こなしているわけではない
You're not truly wearing Junketsu.
What are you talking about?
何を言っている
All you're doing is forcing
your arms through its sleeves.
お前は無理やり
袖を通しているだけだ
Though for a plebeian like you,
that is still quite an impressive feat.
それだけでも凡人にしてみれば
大したものだ
I applaud your efforts.
努力は認めよう だが…
...However...
Wearing outfits that are
...out of your league...
身の丈に合っていない服を
着るのは—
とても醜いことなのだよ
is a most unfashionable thing to do!
（皐月）だあ！
Wearing Junketsu to this battle
was your second huge mistake!
（羅暁）
この戦いに純潔を着てきたことが
大きな過ちだったのだ
もっとも
その力を借りなければ—
Though I'm sure you wouldn't have been able
to even stand in front of me without its help!
私の前に立つことも
できなかったろうがな！
（皐月）
いいかげんなことを言うな！
Enough of your nonsense!
どわっ
Your thought processes
entertained me greatly.
（羅暁）お前の趣向は
十分 楽しませてもらった
But it's about time you
returned Junketsu to me.
そろそろ その純潔
返してもらおう
（流子）あっ
（鮮血）流子 空を
Ryuuko! Look at the sky!
What the hell?
何だ？
...Don't tell me that's...
まさか あれは…
Indeed.
（羅暁）そうだ
あれこそが カバーズ
They are COVERS.
Beings born from the original Life Fiber.
原初生命戦維から
生まれたものたちだ
（流子）き… 鬼龍院皐月
Kiryuuin Satsuki!
How unsightly of you, Kiryuuin Satsuki.
ぶざまなり鬼龍院皐月
これが私に—
Behold the fate of fools that dare
defy me—no, defy the Life Fibers!
いや 生命戦維に逆らう
愚か者の末路だ
You rotten bitch!
てめえ
Ultimately, Satsuki was
never fit to wear Life Fibers.
皐月は所詮 生命戦維を着る器では
なかったということだ
Life Fiber Override:
（羅暁）人衣圧倒 神衣純潔
Godrobe Junketsu.
GODROBE
JUNKETSU
That said, that fool did bring me
someone I never thought I'd meet.
だがその愚か者のおかげで
思わぬ者に出会えたよ
（流子）ハツ
ぐはっ うう…
...That's...
あれは…
Impossible!
何だと…
Matoi Ryuuko,
纏流子
your body has been fused
with Life Fibers, just like mine.
お前も私と同じ
肉体を生命戦維と同化した者
And here I thought you were dead,
お前は死んだはずの
私の娘だったんだよ
daughter of mine!
kurikaesu mainichi ga
My monotonous everyday life
totsuzen iro wo kaeru
Took on a new hue
sonna koto dokka nozonde itanda kedo ne
A part of me always wished for that to happen
iza to naru to
But when it actually did
okubyoumono deshita
I was too scared to act
himitsu ne
That's a secret, okay?
hitori furuete
Trembling alone
soshite kimi ni aitakute
I miss you so much
zutto mikata da yo nante ieta nara
If only I could tell you that I'll always be on your side
muteki
We could be invincible
sou sa tobitatsu toki wa futari de
When we take flight, we'll do so together
tachimukai
We'll make a stand
kakaekirenai okubyou ni
I want to keep smiling
tsuppattatte waratte itai
Even when my cowardice freezes me in place
hitori kiri zutsu ga awasatte
Every little thing will come together
ookina chikara ni naru yo
To give us great strength
ima nee kanjita
That's how I feel right now
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
（鮮血）流子は倒れ
皐月は消え マコすらも行方不明
Ryuuko's down, Satsuki's vanished,
and even Mako's missing!
EVEN MAKO
ヒロイン３人が不在という
最大のピンチ
With all three heroines absent,
the show has hit its biggest crisis.
ABSENT
BIGGEST CRISIS
だが まだ四天王がいる
裸の戦士がいる
HOWEVER
However, the Four Devas are still here.
STILL HERE
The naked warriors are still here.
Show 'em how tough humans can be!
人間のしぶとさ見せてやれ
次回 キルラキル
「たどりついたら いつも雨ふり」
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"Raindrops Keep Falling On My Head"!
EPISODE 19
RAINDROPS KEEP FALLING ON MY HEAD